legitreviews.com 2019-05-26

# Privacy Policy - Legit ReviewsLegit Reviews

## PRIVACY, TERMS, CONDITIONS AND COPYRIGHT

Last Updated: 05/24/2018

**Privacy, Terms, Conditions and Copyright Policy of Legit Reviews, LLC (LegitReviews.com).**

Legit Reviews, LLC takes your privacy seriously and is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy describes and governs the information collection, use, and sharing practices of Legit Reviews, LLC with respect to our websites, mobile applications, and other digital and interactive services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”).

Before you submit any information on or through the Services, please carefully review this Policy together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to therein to understand our views and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. This Policy applies regardless of the device used to access the Services (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future). Some online services offered by or affiliated with Legit Reviews, LLC may be governed by a separate privacy policy. In those instances, the product-specific privacy policy shall apply to that online service.

**Information Collected**

We may collect information from you during your use of or access to the Services, such as when you:

  * Register for an account;
  * Fill in forms;
  * Search for a product,
  * Make a purchase or place an order;
  * Enter a sweepstakes or contest or register for a promotion;
  * Complete a survey or provide us with feedback;
  * Subscribe to a service or request certain features (e.g., newsletters, updates, and other products);
  * Communicate with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise;
  * Report a problem with our website; or
  * Post user-generated content, including comments, to or on any of our Services, including on discussion boards, community forums, or other social media functions on our website.

Legit Reviews does not directly collect any personally identifiable information on our site that is not provided voluntarily. Any personal information voluntarily submitted by the user is treated as confidential, and is not shared with third parties unless required by law enforcement.  Like most all websites, LegitReviews.com automatically logs certain non-personally identifiable information about visits to any of our sites URL’s.  This means that your IP address may be automatically logged, however this is never used to trace you personally except where a potential violation of our Terms and Conditions of Use is concerned. The main reason your IP address is logged as it is used by Google Analytics in conjunctions with third party advertising companies for remarketing information, and demographics and interests reports. This allows you to receive targeted ads and allows Legit Reviews, LLC to see what content is generating traffic. Information collected are IP addresses, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, and other information about your computer or device(s), browser types, browser language, operating system, mobile device carrier information, the state or country from which you accessed the site. This information is used for site administration and for producing usage statistics. We do collect email addresses from individuals that wish to take advantage of special promotional offers, join the forms or sign-up for our mailing lists. We do not sell, rent or disclose collected email addresses to third parties.

**Information From Children**  
Nothing on our services is directed to children under the age of 13 and such children are not permitted to use the Services. If we discover we have received any “personal information” (as defined under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this Policy, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe we have any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us as described below.

**How long we retain your data**

We will keep your information only for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purpose that it has been processed, taking into account any legal requirements under Applicable Law. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

**Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, sound clips etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Cookies  
**We may automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our services and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our services. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services. All cookies will expire after 12 months.

**Third Party Cookies:  **Some of the cookies on the Service are operated by third parties, such as Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+, Reddit, YouTube, Facebook or others. Some of these third parties (for example third-party advertisers) may use cookies on the Service to allow them to deliver the services they are providing. Some of the cookies operated by third parties may be used for analytics purposes, such as to monitor, analyze and prevent fraudulent traffic or other suspicious activities. In order to create a user-friendly experience, some of our third-party promotions and advertisements are designed to automatically transmit users’ information onto the third party’s landing page when you choose to “click” upon a third party’s advertisement or promotion. We do not control these third parties or their use of cookies. This means it is not possible for us to manage these cookies. This Policy only covers the use of cookies by Legit Reviews, LLC and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party. Some of these third party cookies are not session based and have varying expiry dates. Please check the websites of these third parties for details on how they use cookies.

**Geo-Location Information:  **Some devices allow applications to access real-time location-based information (for example, GPS). Some photos or other content you place within the Service may contain recorded location information. We may use this information to optimize your experience. Also, some of the information we collect from a device, for example IP address, can sometimes be used to approximate a device’s location.

**Web Beacons**  
Legit Reviews, LLC and our third party partners may collect information using web beacons (also known as pixel tags). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

**Opt-Out Policy**  
Legit Reviews, LLC gives users options to opt out wherever practical.

**Unsubscribe Policy**  
Users may unsubscribe from any of our electronic newsletters or site notifications at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter or notification. You may also contact Nathan Kirsch by e-mail at nate@legitreviews.com for removal.

**Use of Collected Information**  
Collecting the information described above enables us to tailor our content to our readers’ needs and to target more relevant advertising. If at any time you would like assistance with deleting your data, please contact Nathan Kirsch by e-mail at nate@legitreviews.com

**Third Party Partners**  
Legit Reviews, LLC has teamed up with reputable third party vendors in order to provide certain services to its online users. When leaving our website to view one of our partner websites, we encourage users to review the privacy statements of those websites as we cannot guarantee the privacy of users while visiting affiliate sites.Legit Reviews, LLC may use third-party companies to serve ads or analyze behavior patterns when you visit our Web site. These companies may place or provide ads (such as banner ads) on this Web site that might also place cookies. These companies may use non-personally or personally identifiable information about your visit to our web site in order to help us improve our user experience and/or provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of providing these services or placing these ads, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your computer and each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies.

Our primary partners are the following and we encourage you to visit their privacy policies to see how they might use your data:  
[Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – Google Analytics Tracking, Google Adsnese, Google [DFP Ad Serving](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)  
[Po.st/RythmOne](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy) – Site Social Sharing Widget  
[Disqus](https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy) – Site Comments Engine  
[YouTube](https://policies.google.com/privacy) – Site Video Services  
[IDG Tech Network](https://www.idg.com/gdpr/) – Advertising  
[Vibrant Media](https://www.vibrantmedia.com/privacy-policy/) – Contextual Advertising  
[Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496) – Merchant Sales Services  
[Commission Junction/Conversant Media](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy) – Merchant Sales Services

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform online services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or services. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you can generally control cookies from being put on your computer to deliver tailored advertising, you may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer Opt-Out link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices), the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Opt-Out link](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), the [opt-out page of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/%20), or [TrustArc’s Preference Manager](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. You may also use the links available in advertisements that appear in the Services.

**Use of This Site**  
As a reader or user of LegitReviews.com, you are using the site as a privilege, not a right, free of charge. Therefore the owner and operators of this site may, at any time, at their discretion, disable/ban your user account or prevent your use of this site.

**Indemnity**  
You will indemnify and hold harmless Legit Reviews, LLC, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, customers, vendors, officers and employees from any liability, damage or cost (including reasonable attorneys. fees and cost) from any claim or demand made by any third party or yourself, due to or arising out of your access to the Site, use of the Services, violation of the Terms of Use by you, or the infringement by you, or any third party using your account or LegitReviews.com User ID, or of any intellectual property or other right of any person or entity.

**Acceptance of Terms**  
By using the LegitReviews.com website, you signify your acceptance of this website privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of any LegitReviews.com site following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.

strong style=”font-weight:bold;color:#000;”>International Users  
The Services are operated in the United States and are governed by United States law. If you are a resident of the European Union or other location outside the United States, please be advised that any information you provide through the Services will be transferred to the United States or other designated locations outside of the EEA, which may not have a similar standard for data protection as the laws of your jurisdiction for processing, hosting, and storage by us or our service providers.

**Changes To This Policy**  
We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time to reflect changes in the law, our data collection and use practices, the features of our Services, or advances in technology. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Services following the posting of changes to this Policy will mean you accept those changes.

If you have questions about our privacy or legal policies, contact Nathan Kirsch by e-mail at nate@legitreviews.com.

**Copyright Policy**  
We respect the intellectual property and copyright of others. As such, we have a policy of removing user submissions that violate copyright law, suspending access to our services and to any user who uses the services in violation of copyright law, as well as terminating, in appropriate circumstances, the account of any user who uses our services in violation of copyright law.

Pursuant to Title 17 of the United States Code, Section 512, we have implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed copyright infringement and for processing claims in accordance with the law. If you believe a user on our service is infringing your copyright, please provide written notice on the of claims of copyright infringement and we will expeditiously remove the allegedly infringing material.

**DMCA Notification of Claimed Infringement**  
If you believe that your content has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with written notice that includes the following information:

  * Your name, address, telephone number, and email address.
  * A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed.
  * The URL(s) or a description of where on the LegitReviews.com service the material you claim is infringing is located.
  * A written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the use of the copyrighted work is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.
  * An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest.

Send your notice of claimed copyright infringement to:

Email: copyright@legitreviews.com

Postal mail:  
Legit Reviews, LLC  
P.O. Box  
201 E Allen Street  
Wentzville, MO 63385

If you have questions about our copyright policies, contact Nathan Kirsch by e-mail at nate@legitreviews.com.
